Borns Jewish Studies Program records, 1972-2010 C407
Indiana University Archives
- Multimedia, 1978-1984; undated (Box 7)
  - VHS & ¾", 1978-1991 (Box 12)
    - Portrait of a People Series, 1978; undated (Box 12)
      - Literature of the Holocaust by Alvin Rosenfeld, 1978 (Box 12)
      - Responsa Literature, undated (Box 12)
      - Hebrew Bible, II, undated (Box 12)
      - American Jewish Writings I by Alvin Rosenfeld, 1978 (Box 12)
      - Modern Israeli Literature, undated (Box 12)
      - The Hebrew Bible I, undated (Box 12)
    - Jesus in Jewish and Christian Literature by Alvin Rosenfeld, Pinchas Lapide, and Gerard Sloyan, 1981 (Box 12)
    - Connections: The Jewish Experience in History, Thought, and Music Series, 1980; undated (Box 12)
      - Jewish Tradition in the Modern World, undated (Box 12)
      - The Musical Spirit of a People: The Art of the Cantor by Louis Danto, 1980 (Box 12)
      - The Musical Spirit of a People: The Contemporary Voice by Galit Pinsky, 1980 (Box 12)
      - Recovering the Past, Reclaiming the Future by Todd Endelman, Michael Morgan, and Alvin Rosenfeld, 1980 (Box 12)
    - Friedlander Lecture The New Discourse of Nazism: Part II, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Auschwitz: If You Cried, You Died, (2 copies) (Box 13)
    - 1987-1988 Lecture Series, Dr. Alvin H. Rosenfeld, 2-29-1988 (Box 13)
    - Prof. Fishman's Lecture (Box 13)
    - IU Klezmer Weekend, March 22-24, 1991 (Box 13)
    - Claude Lanzmann Lecture, April 19, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Claude Lanzmann, April 19, 1990 (Box 13)
    - The Holocaust: Life Unworthy of Life- The Witnesses, The Destruction of Families, The Kristallnacht and Ghettos, The 'Final Solution' and its Perpetrators, Planet Auschwitz, The Rescuers (Box 13)
    - Pros and Cons #1505 The Middle East: Must We Abandon Hope for Peace? (Box 13)
    - 1. Finding Home (Siona Segment) 2. Backroad (WSIUTV-8) PBS (Box 13)
    - Brave Old World Kigzmer, 3/91 (Box 13)
    - WNET Heritage: Civilization and the Jews Discussion Leaders Workshop, 12/27/85 (Box 13)
    - 65316 Survivor WCVE Dr. Charles W. Sydnor, Jr. (Box 13)
    - KLEZKAMP 89 (B.O.W. TRIO in concert with Ben Bazyler (Box 13)
    - Jewish Studies Sept 6 Reflections on WWII: A Look Back After 50 Years! Shurstz, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Jewish Studies Promotional Sampler (U-matic) (Box 13)
    - Egyptian Jewish Wedding Film (U-matic) (Box 13)
    - Friedlander Lecture #1 The New Discourse on Nazism I (U-matic), 9-2-1984 (Box 13)